[Music]
[Música]
Ari Tell me something Tell me something that doesn't piss me off
Ari Dime algo Dime algo que no me cabre
Ari eh Ari Gameplays talks about how he's been
Ari eh Ari Gameplays habla de cómo ha
living the last few months of his life
vivido los últimos meses de su vida
after his divorce and says he tries to
luego de su divorcio y dice que intenta
put on his best face even though he's not
poner la mejor cara a pesar de no estar
always well I always come back and
siempre bien yo siempre vengo y les
try to put on my best face I think it's
intento poner mi mejor cara yo creo que
been a long time no no I don't show myself in
hace mucho de verdad no no me muestro de
a vulnerable way to you all
una manera vulnerable ante ustedes
you know that I'm a person who
ustedes saben que yo soy una persona que
has a thousand feelings and also like
tiene mil de sentimientos además como
I'm very sensitive and usually I
que soy muy sensible y por lo general
pretend you can see me when I'm
dejo como que si me vean cuando estoy
down when I'm sad and all that but it's
mal cuando estoy triste y todo eso pero
been like many stages and all this
han sido como muchas etapas e todo este
time I can say something can you imagine if
tiempo puedo decir algo te imaginas que
in a year they get married again Ah no no no
en un año vuelvan a casarse Ah no no no
no Why come on let's make a mess Why do I
no Por qué venga vamos a liarla Por qué
ask myself eh but come on like this it
me pregunto yo eh pero vamos así se me
came to me when I published the clip
vino la cabeza cuando publiqué el clip
okay eh Why did Juan suddenly lose 3
vale eh Por qué de repente Juan pierde 3
kg take off his cap and grow a beard
kg se quita la gorra y se deja la barba
and wow He's hot he's on his [ __ ]
y wow Está buenísimo está en su [__]
Prime how good it's been for him to
Prime qué bien le ha venido de que
take off is you Ari
quitarse encima está ti acaso Ari no
isn't prettier since she's been single
está más guapa desde que está soltera
too but it came to me  so eh it has
también pero se me ha venido así eh se
come to me like this eh She is not, she is not in
me ha venido así eh No está no está en
her [ __ ] Prime too It's that I already
su [__] Prime también Es que esto ya lo
mentioned this the other time and I mentioned it the
comenté la otra vez y yo lo comenté la
other time Of course She as she already took care of herself as she
otra vez Claro Ella como ya se cuidaba
took care of herself before No well of
como ya se cuidaba anteriormente No pues
course the change is not that
claro el cambio como que no es tan
radical but I see her more favored she hasn't had
radica pero yo la veo más favorecida no
surgery she is thinner she has
se ha operado está más delgada se ha
also had surgery on her abdomen no but that is
operado también el abdomen no pero eso
not said but that is not said it has been like
no se dice pero eso no se dice sido como
very chaotic months eh of feeling
meses muy caóticos eh de estar sintiendo
a lot of feeling little of being
mucho de estar sintiendo poco de estar
up of being down where one day
arriba de estar abajo donde un día
I wake up With more desire to do things
amanezco Con más ganas de de hacer cosas
and other days I really just
y otros días de verdad simplemente
want to be lying down and and and flowing in my
quiero estar tirada y y y fluir en mi
bed it has been months of reading a thousand things about
cama ha sido meses de leer mil cosas de
everything I
de todo o
mean Thank you m for those 37 months and tier
sea Gracias m por esos 37 meses y tier
Gang Thank you Thank you very much but well
Gang Thank you Muchas gracias pero pues
I feel that from the moment
yo siento que desde el momento
I came Here I have
uno como que he venido Aquí les he
put on my best face I have shown you that I
puesto mi mejor cara les he enseñado que
am smiling that I am happy
estoy sonriente que estoy feliz
but well really there is like a lot
pero pues realmente hay como mucho
happening I am not this person all the
sucediendo no soy esta persona todo el
time but but well I think that I think that's where we are
tiempo pero pero bien Creo que creo que
going I am putting effort into everything
ahí vamos le estoy echando ganas en todo
too  I've seen that they've tried to
también he visto como que me han querido
drag me into controversies lately and Ah
embarrar en polémicas últimamente y Ah
But she's still a liar, no But she's still a
Pero sigue mentirosa no Pero sigue
liar, no, she's still a liar, of course Here she is
mentirosa no sigue mentirosa claro Aquí
already saying they've tried to drag me
ya está diciendo me han querido embarrar
into controversies, no I mean, she's going to
en polémicas no O sea va a volver a
deny the likes we talked about again she's going to
negar los like de los que hablamos va a
deny the likes again Hey, but
volver a negar los likes Oye pero por
why are you telling me that you don't see
qué me estáis diciendo que no veis bien
Ari well if I see her perfectly well why are you
a Ari si yo la veo perfectamente por me
telling me Javi, turn off the alerts,
estáis diciendo Javi quita las alertas
see you A hari có that you don't see her and there's
nos vemos A hari có que no la veis y hay
mention of me on some topics like I
mención mía de algunos temas como que
think you know that I'm very much into
creo que ustedes saben que estoy muy a
my own thing sometimes I can't even turn on
mi rollo a veces no puedo ni prender
Stream like I would like and I just kind of ignore
Stream como me gustaría y yo simplemente
all the things I like for you all to
como que paso ya de todas las cosas me
realize that I'm into
gusta que se den cuenta que estoy en lo
my own thing and since there are no things like me
mío y ya que no hay cosas como que me
wobbling or moving but nothing I wanted to
tambal o me muevan pero nada quería
thank you because it's good to
agradecerles porque está bien padre
turn on live
prender directo
and places but but places I there are times
y lugares pero pero lugares yo hay veces
that there are things that I don't understand I mean I mean
que hay cosas que no entiendo O sea de O
what do you have to do to make it
sea qué tienes que hacer para que te
appear here or there I mean no no I don't
aparezca aquí o ahí o sea no no no
understand this I didn't understand this clip
entiendo esto no he entendido este clip
the truth is I don't know that we were smoking
la verdad no sé que estábamos fumando
this day eh I mean how how how
este día eh o sea cómo cómo cómo de
suddenly when Ari's clip ends I
repente cuando termina el clip de Ari
appeared there but well but well but
apareci ahí pero bueno pero bueno pero
well I don't know It's been like a little bit it's not
bueno no sé Ha sido como un poco no ha
like a little bit m to speak out but
sido como un poco m pronunciarse pero
also to wash my hands
también para para lavarse las manos
regarding the issue of the controversy the
respecto el tema de la de la polémica
other day with the likes no reven has
del otro día con los likes no reven ha
posted a tweet saying doesn't it seem strange
puesto un tweet dice no parece curioso
that wismichu felipes and others the story
que wismichu felipes y demás hisoria
is over still having promos and
acabada siga teniendo promos y
collaborations the amount of shady dealings and
colaboraciones la de chanchullos y
cronyism behind all that
amiguismo que hay detrás de todo eso
must scare the [ __ ] out of you anything else
debe acojonar al pánico otra cosa no
but the [ __ ] reds are doing
pero los rojos de [__] se lo montan de
great to not do a stroke of work I kind of
lujo para no dar un palo al agua Yo es
lost track of them a little bit
que le perdí un poco bastante la pista
not these people not like what Felipe does
no a esta gente no como lo de Felipe no
has no name what the mother
tiene nombre lo
of God Lili mother of God Lili I
de madre de Dios Lili madre de Dios Lili
couldn't tell you if I'm jealous m
No sabría decirte si soy celosa m
maybe sometimes maybe It depends on what you do if you
quizá a veces tal vez Depende qué hagas
box it or not well it's up to you no
si la cajas o no pues ya queda en ti no
no Why have you sent me this clip I
no Por qué me habéis mandado este clip
really don't understand you Eh I don't understand you
de verdad no os entiendo Eh no os
don't send me these clips
entiendo a mí no me mandéis estos clips
with these intentions no  I already
con estas intenciones no que ya os
know you, [ __ ], they send me, they send me
conozco [__] es que me mandan me manda
the clip, wale, and Javi says, forgive her, don't
el clip wale y me dice Javi perdónala no
criticize her anymore, he sends me a click but
la critiques más me manda un click pero
without gossip, without ch, without anything, I mean, pure
sin salseo sin ch sin nada o sea puro
fan service of the [ __ ], of the [ __ ] s of W of W
fan service del put del [__] s de W de W
Huerta
Huerta
[Music]
[Música]